椒盐脆饼
Pretzel Fang.
洛杉矶
'Los Angeles.
“我称之为斗牛之城
'I call it the City of Bullshitters.
“我该判断谁？
'Who am I to judge?
“我也住在这里
'I live here, too.
这个地方会让你的生活黯然失色
'This place will suck the life right out of you.
有些人自我振作起来
'Some people pick themselves up
在被狗屎击倒后
'after getting the shit knocked out of them.
“其他人像旧的旅行车一样崩溃
'Others break down like an old station wagon.
我们可以试图推迟不可避免的......
'We can try to put off the inevitable...
但最终一切都崩溃了
'but everything breaks down eventually.
即使是一个人的精神
'Even a person's spirit.
“但是穆斯......
'But Moose...
“他是牢不可破的”
'he's unbreakable.'
- 嘿 亚伦 - 巧克力麋
- Hey, Aaron. - Chocolate Moose.
我不能说太久我得到便便
I can't talk too long. I got to poo.
哦
Oh.
所以...
So...
- 你有什么新事？ - 没什么 只是这些小偷
- what's new with you? - Nothing, just these thieves
试图拍摄我的东西
trying to take pictures of my stuff.
看看他们是否可以在易趣上降低价格这是残酷的
See if they can get it cheaper on eBay. It's brutal.
你想知道我的新鲜事吗？
You wanna know what's new with me?
你在我的“荒地”海报上获得了马丁·辛的亲笔签名吗？
You got Martin Sheen's autograph on my "Badlands" poster?
不我今晚要和亨特·邓巴一起去参加派对
Nope. I'm going to a party tonight with Hunter Dunbar.
- 真的吗？ - 是的
- Really? - Yep.
- 亨特邓巴？ - 是的
- Hunter Dunbar? - Yep.
怎么会这样？
How'd that happen?
我被邀请参加演员和工作人员聚会
I got invited to the cast and crew party
- “星期五晚上的杀手” - 嗯！
- of "The Friday Night Killer". - Huh!
好吧 有人正在向世界移动
Well, somebody's moving up in the world.
嗯 这很酷 但......
Well, that's cool, but...
我自己会有很多邓巴的亲笔签名
I'm gonna have a lot of Dunbar autographs myself
- 这个周末过后 - 哦耶？为什么？
- after this weekend. - Oh, yeah? Why's that?
他要进店了
He's coming into the store.
你是驼鹿你不知道这个？
You're the Moose. You don't know this?
什么？
What?
他明天晚上正在签署他的新书
He's signing copies of his new book tomorrow night.
- 什么？ - 这里
- What? - Here.
啊
Ah.
你为什么不告诉我这实际上是在发生？
Why didn't you tell me this was actually happening?
它刚刚结合在一起我应该做些什么？
It just came together. What am I supposed to do?
用你的轻便摩托车打电话给你？
Call you on your moped?
他是签约收藏品还是书？
Is he signing collectibles or just the book?
不 只是这本书你必须在这里买
No, just the book. And you got to buy it here,
你必须有一张收据我正在查
and you got to have a receipt. I'm checking.
我家里有一些特别的东西
I got some special things at home,
但我需要一些特别的东西
but I need something super special.
好吧 你已经掌握了我们得到的所有东西
Well, you've had your mitts on just about everything we got.
我们得到了那些大堂车 还有一个 两个和四个卡弗
We got those lobby cars, and the Carver one, two, and four.
有人偷了三个人
Somebody fucking stole three.
“鬼火车”英国四驱车
The British Quad for "Ghost Train".
你是个白痴 “幽灵列车”是如此典型
You are such an idiot. "Ghost Train" is so typical.
我需要一些东西......我需要......我需要一些值得记住的东西
I need something... I need... I need something rememberable.
这是一个字 穆斯？
Is that a word, Moose?
好吧 这个白痴还有......这件背心
Well, this idiot still has... this vest.
那是“太空吸血鬼”
That's "Space Vampires".
- 还是800美元吗？ - 听着
- Is it still $800? - Listen,
它从来都不是穆斯系列中的一个项目
it's never really been an item in the Moose range.
是的 但要让它更便宜瞧瞧你...
Yeah, but make it cheaper. Look, you...
我有多少次来这家商店？
How many times do I come in here to this store?
我花多少次辛苦赚来的钱
How many times do I spend my hard-earned money
在收银台？
in that cash register?
我们有多少次进行过这样的讨论？
And how many times have we had this exact discussion?
我得到了300美元 这就是我的全部
I got $300, that's all I have.
请让我有背心请？
Please let me have the vest. Please?
请？
Please?
我不知道为什么对我这么难
I don't know why it is so hard for me
对你说不 穆斯
to say no to you, Moose.
我要300美元
I want your $300,
我希望你能在今年年底之前支付
and I want you to pay it by the end of this year.
是的先生！
Yes, sir!
我希望你拥有它
I want you to have it.
并且明天也不要忘记它
And don't forget it tomorrow either.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
麋 这是愚蠢的把它放在后面
Moose, that's stupid putting it on backwards.
我知道
I know.
邓巴先生 很高兴见到你
It's a pleasure to meet you, Mr. Dunbar.
好啦好啦
Come on, come on.
邓巴先生 很高兴见到你
It's a pleasure to meet you, Mr. Dunbar.
我有你的每一个VHS和DVD
I have every one of your VHS's and DVD's.
就像每个人都这样说的那样说点什么......
It's, like, everybody says that. Say something sm...
我不...我...
I don't... I'm...
说些不同的东西
Say something different.
说些什么......不 我应该告诉他......
Say something... No, I should tell him...
哦 天哪 他会喜欢这个
Oh, oh, my God, he'll love this.
你真的是“吸血鬼杀手”
You were really rad in "Vampire Killers".
哦？
Oh?
你要我用你的名字给你打电话？
You want me to call you by your first name?
嗨 亨特这是一件独一无二的衬衫
Hi, Hunter. This is a one and only shirt,
但我可以告诉你在哪里......得到它
but I could tell you where to... get it,
但那里不会有任何东西
but there won't be any there.
他会爱我的他会爱我的！
He's gonna love me. He's gonna love me!
“我把一些责任归咎于自己
'I put some of the blame on myself.
“我只是想成为一个好朋友”
'I just wanted to be a good friend.'
我不知道他们是什么
你不能去一家五金店吗？
我的意思是 邓巴必须值得去小家得宝之旅
他确定你觉得他会喜欢我的衬衫吗？
嘿 穆斯对不起 我来晚了
Hey, Moose. Sorry I'm late.
什么花了你这么久 莉娅？
What took you so long, Leah?
我在这里等了200个小时
I've been waiting here, like, 200 hours.
- 我知道 - 说真的 我要离开了
- I know. - Seriously, I was gonna leave.
抱歉对不起好？
Sorry. I'm sorry. OK?
无论如何 这个派对刚刚起步
The party's just starting to ramp up anyway.
你带刀具了吗？
Did you bring the cutters?
剪刀 伙计？
Scissors, dude?
我说断线钳
I said bolt cutters.
I don't know what they are.
我说断线钳
Couldn't you just go to a hardware store?
I mean, Dunbar has to be worth a trip to little Home Depot.
我说断线钳
He sure is. You think he'll like my shirt?
就像我最好的恐怖衬衫一样
This is, like, my best horror shirt.
- 你觉得他会喜欢吗？ - 是的 他会......他会喜欢的
- Do you think he'll like it? - Yeah, he'll... he'll like it.
你知道吗？我们将以老式的方式做到这一点
You know what? We're gonna do this the old fashioned way.
好的 你会起床的
OK, you're gonna get up here.
你要把脚放在我的手里
You're gonna put your foot into my hand.
你会达到高 然后......
You're gonna reach high, and then...
你会拉扯自己 好吗？
you'll pull yourself over, OK?
好的
Alright.
向上
Up.
一二三
One. Two. Three.
哇 耐莉
Whoa, Nelly.
这是...
It's ju...
哦 我的上帝驼鹿 你还好吗？
Oh, my God. Moose, are you OK?
我还好吗？
Am I alright?
我的意思是 你听起来不错
I mean, you sound alright.
我的衬衫好吗？
Is my shirt alright?
我确定你的衬衫很好
I'm sure your shirt is fine.
这不是个好主意！
This is not a good idea!
刚刚得到亨特邓巴的亲笔签名和分裂 好吗？
Just get Hunter Dunbar's autograph and split, OK?
嘿先生 我可以帮你喝一杯吗？
Hey there. Can I get you a drink, sir?
Hey there. Can I
get you a drink, sir?
- 嗯？ - 我可以给你买个饮料吗？
- Hmm? - Can I get you a drink?
我会吃草莓奶昔
I'll just have a strawberry milkshake
请用真正的冰淇淋
with real ice cream, please.
是的 我们不......我们没有奶昔
Yeah, we don't... we don't have milkshakes,
但我可以给你一杯鸡尾酒或倒给你一杯苏打水？
but I can make you a cocktail or pour you a soda?
不用了 谢谢我只是想动摇
No, thanks. I just want a shake.
- 我可以问你一个问题？ - 当然
- May I ask you a question? - Sure.
- 亨特邓巴今晚在这儿吗？ - 谁？
- Is Hunter Dunbar here tonight? - Who?
亨特·邓恩 ......
Hunter Dun...
对不起 阿曼达？对不起 阿曼达？
Excuse me, Amanda? Excuse me, Amanda?
你好
Hi.
你今晚怎么样？
How are you this evening?
嗯 我很好 谢谢你呢？
Um, I'm wonderful, thank you. And you?
我很好谢谢你的慰问
I'm just fine. Thank you for asking.
- 嗯嗯 - 你的......你的电影真棒
- Mm-hmm. - Your... Your movie is amazing,
你会变得很棒
and you're going to be amazing in it.
- 谢谢真是太好了 - 我喜欢你的衬衫
- Thank you. That's so sweet. - I love your shirt.
它是世界上唯一的一个
It's the only one in the world.
嗯
Hmm.
阿万达 我真是你的忠实粉丝
I'm a really big fan of yours, Amanda.
我真的觉得你的工作很扎实 几分钟到几天
I really think your work is solid and minutes into days,
而且我认为你在“杀死或被杀”方面真的很棒
and I think you're really good in "Kill or Be Killed".
你应该做更多的恐怖图片 阿曼达
You should do more horror pictures, Amanda.
是啊
Yeah.
你是一个伟大的决赛女孩
You're a great Final Girl.
你当然知道我的工作
You certainly know my work.
是啊
Yeah.
你知道亨特·邓巴今晚在哪里吗？
Do you know where Hunter Dunbar is tonight?
呃......猎人？嗯 你知道
Uh... Hunter? Well, you know,
我相信亨特正在他儿子的小学打球
I believe Hunter is at his son's elementary school play.
你知道 所有这些孩子都必须思考
You know, all those kids must think
猎人是一个真实的动作英雄
that Hunter is some, sorta like, real-life action hero.
- 好极了！ - 哦！
- Great! - Oh!
不允许外包装
No outside bags allowed.
我需要......我需要得到阿曼达的亲笔签名
I need... I need to get an autograph from Amanda.
让我有一张签名 阿曼达
Just let me have one autograph, Amanda.
这就够了 我们走吧来吧
That's enough, let's go. Come on.
不 不......你......不要让他这样对我 阿曼达
No, don't... You... Don't let him do this to me, Amanda.
我是一个粉丝我是她的头号粉丝
I'm a fan. I'm her number one fan.
停下来！停下来！
Stop it! Stop it!
停下来！我来这里看亨特邓巴
Stop it! I came here to see Hunter Dunbar.
莉亚！莉亚！莉亚！
Leah! Leah! Leah!
是谁呀？
Who is it?
打开门！
Open the door!
我只想要签名！
I just wanted an autograph!
打开门 穆斯！
Open the door, Moose!
我把脖子贴在你的身上
I put my neck on the line for you,
这样你就可以继续你那怪异的小爱好了
so that you could continue with your freaky little hobby
收集像孩子一样的亲笔签名
collecting autographs like a child,
这就是你如何报答我的？表现得像个疯子？
and this is how you repay me? By acting like a maniac?
“疯子” 这是一部很棒的电影不是糟糕的翻拍
"Maniac", that's a great movie. Not the crappy remake.
那被高估了这是我喜欢的新款
That was overrated. It's the new one I like.
- 请勿更改主题 - 是的 它......
- Don't change the subject. - It was, it...
利亚 是阿曼达把我踢出去了
It was Amanda who got me kicked out, Leah.
她是一个庆祝者
She was the one being a celebutard.
好吧 没关系 穆斯 好吗？
Well, it doesn't matter, Moose, OK?
因为我必须支付租金 而这台相机就是我这样做的
Because I have to pay the rent, and this camera is how I do it.
如果你不能尊重
If you can't respect that,
那是我为你做的最后一件事
then this is the last favor I'm ever doing for you.
亨特·邓巴昨晚甚至不在场
Hunter Dunbar wasn't even there last night.
你答应他会在那里
You promised that he'd be there.
不要......抬起你的声音
Do not... raise... your voice at me.
不好看 穆斯
Not a good look, Moose.
我可以做我想做的事你不是我的妈妈
I can do what I want. You're not my mom.
那是歇斯底里的
That was hysterical.
胡说！
Poppycock!
你好欢迎来到好 ...欢迎来到好莱坞
Hello. Welcome to Hol... Welcome to Hollywood.
欢迎来到好莱坞......
Welcome to Hollywood...
在哪里做梦
where dreams are made of.
梦想成真的地方
Place where dreams are made of.
做梦的地方......
Where dreams are made...
伦敦桥就在那边
London Bridge is right over there.
结束了...
It's over...
甲壳虫乐队在这里！甲壳虫乐队在这里！
The Beatles are here! The Beatles are here!
- 你好 特里西 - “你好 特雷西”
- Hello, Tricy. - 'Hello, Tracy.'
你好 特里西
Hello, Tricy.
开膛手杰克开膛手杰克
Jack the Ripper. Jack the Ripper.
怎么了 洛杉矶？
What's up, LA?
我是林荫大道的首映多媒体艺人
I am the Boulevard's premiere multimedia entertainer,
和极端表演艺术家在这里让你大吃一惊......
and extreme performance artist here to astonish you...
让你喘不过气来好的？
and leave you breathless. Alright?
现在 我的名字是托德......
Now, my name is Todd...
但有些人 他们称我为托德神好的？
but some folks, they call me Todd the God. Alright?
而且我要打击你的思想 好吗？
And I'm about to blow your minds, alright?
现在你们都来看了一场精彩的表演吧？
Now you all came to see an amazing show, right?
是啊！
Yeah!
好吧 现在在我向你证明之前
Alright, now before I prove to you
我是大道上最核心的魔术师
that I am the most hardcore illusionist on the Boulevard,
我可以请一些勇敢的灵魂为我测试这个钉子
can I please get some brave soul to test this nail for me
证明这不是假的？
to prove it's not a fake?
嘘！嘘！
Shh! Shh!
那是“奎因”吗？
Is that the "Quine"?
伙计们 你听到了这是真的...而且很难
You heard it hear, folks. It's real... and it's hard.
好的
Alright.
哦耶！哈哈！
Oh, yeah! Ha-ha!
伙计 我喜欢这个狗屎！
Man, I love this shit!
喔！来吧 来吧 把你的钱拿出来
Whoo! Come on, come on, get your money out.
马上钱在这些桶里
Right now. Money in these buckets.
来吧 看看这个啊...
Come on, look at this. Ah...
我们去 继续他们的到来让他们来吧来吧
There we go, keep 'em coming. Keep 'em coming. Come on.
这是独一无二的娱乐活动
This is one-of-a-kind entertainment right here.
就在好莱坞的街道上！托德上帝 宝贝！
Right on the streets of Hollywood! Todd the God, baby!
喔！
Whoo!
- 伙计 这真的吗？ - 那个 混蛋？
- Man, is this really it? - How about that, motherfucker?
我正在做他妈的所有危险工作
I'm doing all the fucking dangerous work.
- 他妈的 瘦！ - 哦耶？咦？
- Fuck you, Slim! - Oh, yeah? Huh?
- 是的 去他妈的 - 祝你好运 你他妈的猫！
- Yeah, go fuck yourself. - Good luck, you fucking pussy!
- 滚开！ - 一块狗屎
- Fuck off! - Piece of shit.
他妈的笨蛋......嘿 驼鹿！
Fucking bullshi... Hey, Moose!
嘿 老兄 为什么洗？对斯母的行为感到抱歉
Hey, man, why the wash? Sorry about Slim's behavior.
我得走了 托德我正在和亨特邓巴见面
I got to go, Todd. I'm meeting with Hunter Dunbar.
- 猎人哑铃 对吧？ - 亨特邓巴！
- Hunter Dumbbell, huh? - Hunter Dunbar!
他恰巧是这个星球上最好的演员
He happens to be the best actor on the planet.
好吧 好吧 为什么你没有介绍我 穆斯？
OK, well, why haven't you introduced me, Moose?
托德 我甚至都不认识他
I don't even know him yet, Todd.
我们以后可以这样做现在 我得到了你的主张
We can do that later. Right now, I got to proposition for you.
苗条和我 我们刚结束了我们的伙伴关系
Slim and I, we just ended our partnership,
我希望你能为他填写好的？
and I want you to fill in for him. Alright?
- 我不想 - 看 这很简单 好吗？
- I don't want to. - Look, it's easy, OK?
我做了所有努力催眠群众
I do all the hard work hypnotizing the masses,
你只需要挑几个口袋
you just need to pick a couple pockets.
我不想 托德！
I don't want to, Todd!
你不尊重大道 你不尊重球迷
You don't respect the Boulevard and you don't respect the fans.
- 而且我不会偷人 - 人？人？
- And I don't steal from people. - People? People?
他们不是人 穆斯！他们是他妈的游客！
They're not people, Moose! They're fucking tourists!
- 驼鹿 你去过哪里？ - 它还没有结束 是吗？
- Moose, where you been? - It's not over yet, is it?
放松 放松我们必须让你排队
Relax, relax. We've got to get you in line.
- 你有背心吗？ - 我确定他会签名吗？
- Have you got the vest? - I sure do. Is he gonna sign?
- 他会签名吗？ - 麋鹿 嘘
- Is he gonna sign? - Moose, shh.
- 直接进去 - 哟 伙计 冷静
- Go right in. - Yo, man, chill.
- 对不起 - 我勒个去？
- I'm sorry. - What the hell?
- 我看得见 看得见标记 - 很好凉
- I got Vis a Vis markers. - Yeah, great. Cool.
- 如果需要 您可以使用一个 - 太棒了
- You can use one if you want. - Awesome.
我是谁来制作这个？
Who am I making this out to?
- 是的 呃 亚历克斯 - 亚历克斯亚历克斯
- It's, uh, Alex. - Alex. Alex.
“为......亚历克斯 祝福......”
"To... Alex, best wishes..."
- 你走了- 谢谢
- There you go. - Thanks.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢祝你有美好的一天
Thank you. Have a good day.
谢谢你的到来
Thanks for coming by.
邓古巴先生 对不起有一个名叫布伦达的女人回来了吗？
Excuse me, Mr. Dunbar. There's a woman named Brenda out back?
她说她需要跟你说话
She says she needs to speak to you.
说它很重要我不知道
Says it's important. I don't know.
好
OK.
- 好的 - 它刚刚回到这里
- Alright. - It's just out back over here.
劳驾
Excuse me.
- 亚伦 他要走了 - 哦 嘛 ......
- Aaron, he's leaving. - Oh, Moo...
- 他会签名吗？ - 驼鹿......
- Is he gonna sign? - Moose...
- 亚伦 他要走了 - 驼鹿 没关系
- Aaron, he's leaving. - Moose, it's OK.
- 他会签名吗？ - 穆斯 他会签名
- Is he gonna sign? - Moose, he's gonna sign.
哦
Oh.
嗨朋友
Hey, buddy.
你到底在这做什么？
What the hell you doing here?
也许你还记得我今晚有约会
Maybe you could remember that I have date tonight.
你说你要看坦纳
You said you'd watch Tanner.
- 今晚？ - 邓巴先生？
- Tonight? - Mr. Dunbar?
- 看 我搞砸了 - 邓巴先生
- Look, I messed up. - Mr. Dunbar.
我是下一个粉丝我想你忘了
I was the next fan in line. I think you forgot.
只是......放轻松 伙计别紧张
Just... just take it easy, buddy. Take it easy.
- 我肯定会 - 给我一点时间 好吗？
- I sure will. - Just give me a minute, OK?
我肯定会邓巴先生 谢谢你
I sure will. Thank you, Mr. Dunbar.
你以为把他带到这里可以吗？
You thought it was OK to bring him here?
这不行
It's not OK.
好的 好的好好
OK, alright. OK. OK.
我...我很抱歉我搞砸了
I'm... I'm sorry. I fucked up.
是啊
Yeah.
显然 这对你来说意味着很多
Clearly this means a lot to you.
显然
Clearly.
你知道我要做什么吗？
You know what I'm gonna do?
明天我要给你打电话
Tomorrow I'm gonna call you
你可以卸载你要卸载的任何东西
and you can unload whatever it is you want to unload on me.
把它全部放在胸前 好吗？
Get it all off your chest, OK?
你真是个狗屎 亨特
You're so full of shit, Hunter.
但你是一个伟大的演员
But you're a great actor.
你有三十分钟
You got thirty minutes.
他妈的！
Fuck!
我是支持你的
I'm on your side.
邓巴先生 你是最棒的你是最好的
You're the best, Mr. Dunbar. You're the best.
你需要学习一些他妈的举止 哥们
You need to learn some fucking manners, buddy.
对不起 邓巴先生 但......
I'm sorry, Mr. Dunbar, but...
I'm sorry, Mr.
Dunbar, but...
我有每个VHS 我有每张DVD
I'm sorry, Mr. Dunbar, but...
I have every VHS, I have every DVD.
你在“勇士”中如此痴迷
You're so rad in "Warriors",
我只是不希望你不签署我的东西
I just don't want you not to sign my stuff.
你来到这个地方 但我正式完成了
You came to the place, but I'm officially done.
但是等到你看到我的特殊物品
But wait till you see the special items I have.
这是“太空吸血鬼”
This is "Space Vampires".
我用他妈的拳头签了你的脸怎么样？
How about I sign your face with my fucking fists?
这是收藏家的项目 你不想带回家
That's a collector's item you're not gonna want to take home.
相信我
Trust me.
是的先生
Yes, sir.
我可以问你一个问题吗？
Can I ask you a question?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
你们怎么找到名人的房子？
How do you guys find celebrity houses?
你是怎么找到他们的？
How do you find them?
你为什么要问？
Why do you ask?
嗯 这很难吗？
Well, is it difficult?
找到名人的房子难吗？
Is it difficult to find famous people's houses?
好吧 呃......我的意思是 有时它可能很棘手
Well, uh... Well, I mean, sometimes it can be tricky,
但我们有自己的方式
but we have our ways.
你认为......这会很难
Do you think that... that it would be difficult
找到亨特·邓巴的房子？
to find Hunter Dunbar's house?
我想不出一个很好的理由
I can't think of one good reason
为什么你们所有人都应该知道亨特·邓巴住在哪里
why you, of all people should know where Hunter Dunbar lives.
why you, of all people
should know where Hunter Dunbar lives.
我只是......我想看看他有多成功
I just... I wanna see how successful he is.
好凉
OK. Cool.
嗯......好吧 如果我想得到一个非常尴尬的镜头
Um... well, if I want to get a really embarrassing shot
他的浴袍里有一些悬挂的庆祝者
of some hung-over celebutard in his bathrobe
在其他一些名人家里
at some other celebutard's house,
我使用我方便的花花公子星图应用程序
I use my handy dandy Star Map app.
- 星地图应用程序？ - 是的
- Star Map app? - Yeah.
它是...
It is...
在那里
right there.
圣母 蝙蝠侠
Holy cow, Batman.
- 很酷 对吗？ - 这是真的吗？
- Pretty cool, right? - Is this for real?
是啊好吧 有时候 我的意思是 如果地址错了
Yeah. Well, sometimes, I mean, if the address is wrong
你还会看到一个名人
you'll still see a celebrity,
因为 我的意思是 他们都住在那里
because, I mean, they all live up there.
无论哪种方式 对我而言 你知道吗？
So either way, cha-ching for me, you know?
啊
Ah.
好我正在下载
OK. I'm downloading.
等等 穆斯您...
Wait, Moose. You...
你必须答应我 好吗？
You have to promise me, OK?
你必须要小心
You have to be careful.
我不希望你被指控跟踪
I don't want you to be accused of stalking.
那真好笑
That's hilarious.
- I'm not an idiot. - No. I know you're not.
- I'm not an idiot.
- No. I know you're not.
- 我不是白痴 - 不 我知道你不是
- I'm not an idiot. - No. I know you're not.
好的你可以有一个
Alright. You can have one.
- 一个？ - 对
- One? - Yup.
谢谢
Thanks.
我爱你 穆西
I love you, Moosey.
我爱你
I love you.
利亚 接机 接机 接机拾起！
Leah, pick up, pick up, pick up. Pick up!
- 你好？ - 莉娅！我要感谢你了
- Hello? - 'Leah! I got to thank you.'
谢谢 非常感谢你
Thank you, thank you, so much.
“好吧 冷静下来谢谢你的意见？
'OK, calm down. Thank me for what?'
星图应用这很棒！
The Star Map app. It's awesome!
它是如此真棒本阿弗莱克的家
It's so awesome. Ben Affleck's house.
“我看到了他的房子它好大
'I saw his house. It's so big.
“你知道他有两个游泳池吗？”
'Did you know he has two pools?'
詹姆斯佛朗哥离我15分钟路程
And James Franco lives 15 minutes away from me.
十五分钟他几乎是我的邻居
Fifteen minutes. He's practically my neighbor.
而杰米·李·柯蒂斯 她的酒吧真是太棒了它太大了 莉娅
And Jaime Lee Curtis, her bar is so big. It's so big, Leah.
好的 穆斯
OK, Moose.
记得我说的 好吗？
Just remember what I said, OK?
别担心别担心请不要担心
Don't worry. Don't worry. Please don't worry.
好的 莫西出去了​​我要走了我要走了
OK, Moosey out. I got to go. I got to go.
亲爱的邓巴先生
'Dear Mr. Dunbar,
“我在写你是因为我真的很在乎你
'I am writing you because I really care about you.
“我在好莱坞书店和海报店见过你
'I met you at the Hollywood Book and Poster Shop.
“你明确表示我打扰了你
'You made it clear that I bothered you,
“这是我想做的最后一件事”
'and that's the last thing I wanted to do.'
“我看过你们所有的电影
'I have seen all your movies.
“我爱 爱 爱他们
'I love, love, love them.
“但我排队等了一个多小时才见到你
'But I waited in line for over an hour to meet you,
你甚至没有花时间
'and you didn't even take the time
给我一张签名
'to give me one autograph.
“我甚至花了我所有的钱买你的背心”
'I even spent all my money to buy your vest.'
哦耶我会画一张......背心的照片
Oh, yeah. I'll draw a picture of... the vest.
请花更多时间向粉丝们展示
'Please take more time to show your fans
“你有多关心他们
'how much you care about them.
“没有我们 你什么都不是”
'Without us, you're nothing.'
这是要做到的
This is gonna do it.
“附:请你签上我的背心
'P.S. Will you please sign my vest
“在社交媒体上关注我？”
'and follow me on social media?'
爱...
'Love...
驼鹿
'Moose.'
28 ...好吧
284 ...
嘿!
Hey!
嘿
Hey.
我可以帮你吗？
Can I help you?
嘿 丹尼你为什么不进屋内一秒钟
Hey, Danny. Why don't you go inside the house for a second
并启动游戏机 好吗？
and fire up the Xbox, alright?
我马上就到了
I'll be in in a minute.
嗨 丹尼嗨 丹尼
Hi, Danny. Hi, Danny.
我不知道你在我家外面做了什么
I don't know what you're doing outside my house
就像一些聋哑人 静音变态 但我建议你继续前进
like some deaf, mute pervert, but I suggest you keep moving.
除非你想要麻烦
Unless you want trouble.
- 你想要麻烦吗？ - 我当然不会我当然不会
- You want trouble? - I sure don't. I sure don't.
这是给你的一封信
Here's a letter for you.
- 这是一封信 - 你写了一封信？
- It's a letter. - You wrote a letter?
我不接受这里的来信
I don't accept letters here.
听着 朋友 我不知道你是怎么找到我的
Listen, pal, I don't know how you found me,
但我再也不想在这附近见到你了
but I don't ever want to see you in this neighborhood again.
好？你明白？
OK? You understand?
邓巴先生 我只想要你的亲笔签名
I just want your autograph, Mr. Dunbar.
我收集签名我买了你的......
I collect autographs. And I bought your...
我从“吸血鬼杀手”买了你的背心
I bought your vest from "Vampire Killers".
这是300美元看到？
It was $300. See?
什么 你是一个怪异的亲笔签名猎犬
What, are you some sorta freak autograph hound
那不会让我独自一人吗？
that won't leave me the fuck alone?
你不能只是来我的私人住宅
You can't just come to my private residence
找我
looking for me.
你想要我的亲笔签名吗？
You want my autograph?
把笔给我
Give me the pen.
谢谢
Thank you.
我收到了你的亲笔签名
I got your autograph.
在那里...
Right there...
是我的亲笔签名
Is my autograph.
现在他妈的离开这里
Now get the fuck out of here.
“他们说你永远不应该遇见你的英雄
'They say you should never meet your heroes.
“但遇到他们不是问题
'But meeting them's not the problem.
“就在你离得太近的时候
'It's when you get too close.
足够接近 看看面具背后是什么
'Close enough to see what's behind the mask.
“这是他们不希望你越过的一条线”
'That's a line they don't want you to cross.'
“小 小男孩
'Ello, little boy.
你想和我合影吗？
You want to take a photograph with me?
- ...我的伴侣戴夫 - 你看到我的伴侣戴夫了吗？
- '...my mate Dave.' - Did you see my mate Dave?
别担心
'No worries.'
我知道 我不是真的来自伦敦吗？
I'm not really from London, you know?
很多人都认为我来自伦敦
A lot of people think I'm from London.
但我不是
But I'm not.
来吧！
Come on!
- 你似乎知道你的东西 - 我确定我确定
- You seem to know your stuff. - I sure do. I sure do.
但不像那个托德家伙
But not like that Todd guy.
他不是上帝他充满了嘟-嘟
He's not a God. He's full of doo-doo.
他不尊重好莱坞我......我尊重好莱坞是啊
He doesn't respect Hollywood. I... I respect Hollywood. Yeah.
好吧 真爱？
Alright, true love?
你真的很好你真的很好
You're really good. You're really good.
你真是太棒了让我......
You're so good. Let me just...
回家之前别忘了去看蜡像馆
Don't forget to see the Wax Museum before you go home.
啊! 苏 他妈的盖洛德？
Ah! 'Sup, fucking gaylord?
嘿 嘿 哦 哦官员 不要逮捕我
Hey, hey, oh, oh. Don't arrest me, Officer.
不是我不 我发誓
It wasn't me. No, I swear.
我发誓我甚至不知道她还在上高中
I swear I didn't even know she was still in high school.
他没有
He didn't.
啊 你在这做什么 穆斯 是吗？
Ah, what you doing here, Moose, huh?
你赚了一些钱吗？
Did you make some serious money?
- 不 这很慢 - 哦 慢 对吧？
- No, it was pretty slow. - Oh, slow, huh?
你叫那么慢？看到？
You call that slow? See?
我......我叫那个球
I... I call that ball.
有点假血一点电影魔术
A little fake blood. A little movie magic.
你喜欢电影 不是吗 穆斯？
You like movies, don't you, Moose?
那是什么了来吧伙计我们庆祝吧
That's what's up. Come on, dude. Let's celebrate.
你做的是荣誉 斯母你他妈的今天赢了
You do the honors, Slim. You fucking earned it today.
你知道 我认为他应该做到荣誉
You know, I think he should do the honors.
你想做这些荣誉吗？
Would you like to do these honors?
- 我觉得他妈的会！ - 是的 吮吸它 是吗？
- I think he fuckin' would! - Yeah, suck it, huh?
天啊！
Oh, man!
哟 当我高 这就像天上的雨水
Yo, when I'm high, it's like the money rains from the heavens,
进入我的口袋
right into my pocket.
那你为什么要偷人呢？
Then why do you steal from people?
- 你为什么偷人？ - 哇 哇 你说什么？
- Why do you steal from people? - Whoa, whoa, what'd you say?
关于偷东西的事情？
Something about stealing?
你没有说什么
You didn't say nothing.
这就是你要保留它的方式
And that's the way you're gonna keep it.
让这家伙休息一下
Give the guy a break.
他正在那里工作 做对了只是...
He's working his ass off out there, do righty. Just...
他只是做了一点与我们不同的事情
He just does it a little bit different than we do.
- 这里一切都好吗？ - 是的
- Everything OK in here? - Yeah.
我们只是谈论道奇队 迪克
We're just talking about the Dodgers, Dick.
为什么你不能让这个人独自一人 对吧？
Why can't you leave this guy alone, huh?
现在离开这里 你退化了
Now get out of here, you degenerates.
再见 穆西
Bye-bye, Moosey.
麋鹿 两只眼睛盯着你
Keepin' two eyes on you, Moose.
那不是很好 迪克
That's not very nice, Dick.
好？
OK?
你为什么要让那些怪胎像你那样推动你？
Why are you letting those freaks push you around like that?
他们只是在玩耍
They're just playing.
你是一个好人 穆斯！
You're a good guy, Moose!
你不应该搞乱那些傻瓜
You shouldn't be messing around with those fools.
他们只是在玩耍
They're just playing.
你不能让人们继续对你说话
You can't let people keep shitting on you.
有一天 你需要学习
One day, you're gonna need to learn
如何为自己挺身而出
how to stand up for yourself.
你将不得不学习如何反击
You're gonna have to learn how to fight back.
好？
OK?
我迟到了
I'm late.
我得走了
I've got to go.
我不知道
'I have no idea
为什么穆斯会回到那个男人的家里
'why Moose would go back to that man's house.
但我想当你找到饼干罐时......
But I suppose when you find the cookie jar...
很难不再回头了
it's hard to not go back for more.
我做的我做的
I did it. I did it.
亨特·邓巴为什么会让这个死？
Why would Hunter Dunbar let this die?
嘿!
Hey!
出去！
Get out!
离开这里！
Get out of here!
你在做什么？你试图让我心脏病发作？
What are you doing? You trying to give me a heart attack?
当然不是
Of course not.
你不能只是偷偷摸摸那样的人 穆斯
You can't just sneak up on people like that, Moose.
我几乎有一个康拉德霍尔走出地球酒吧的镜头
I almost had a shot of Conrad Hall walking outta Earth Bar.
地球酒吧很糟糕 - 没有奶昔
Earth Bar sucks - no milkshakes.
是的 好吧 你最好的朋友亨特邓巴的联合主演
Yeah, well, your best friend Hunter Dunbar's co-star,
泰德女士 早些时候走了出去
Ms. Title, walked out of there earlier
并且用透明的衬衫祝福我 没有胸罩
and blessed me with a see-through blouse, no bra.
你提到邓巴很有趣
It's funny that you mention Dunbar.
因为我就在他家
Because I was just at his house.
- 你在开玩笑 对吧？ - 不
- You're kidding, right? - Nope.
我使用了星图应用程序 就是你告诉我的那个
I used the Star Map app, the one that you told me about.
带你直接去他家和...
Takes you directly to his house. And...
他的植物 他应该更好地照顾他的植物
His plants, he should take better care of his plants.
我没有告诉你使用星图应用程序
I did not tell you to use the Star Map app.
- 你确实做到了 - 不 我没有
- You sure did. - No, I did not.
我告诉过你这个应用程序
I told you about the app
因为你是我认识的最大的电影迷 我想
because you are the biggest movie fan I know, and I thought
你会看到明星居住的地方
you'd get a kick out of seeing where the stars live.
你不能只是侵犯人们的隐私
You cannot just invade people's privacy.
利亚 我没有遇到麻烦
I'm not in trouble, Leah.
我刚刚在他的家里放了一封信 就是这样
I just dropped a letter off at his house, that was it.
穆斯 这真的很糟糕
Moose, this is really bad.
我不敢相信你的表现就像这样
I can't believe you're acting like this.
我以为你会为我感到高兴
I thought you'd be happy for me.
为你感到高兴？
Happy for you?
我从来没有鼓励过你
I would have never encouraged you
如果我知道你会变成一个令人毛骨悚然的小缠扰者
if I knew you'd turn into a creepy little stalker.
我不是跟踪者莉莉 我是粉丝！
I am not a stalker. I am a fan, Leah!
你应该比任何人都更清楚
You should know that better than anybody.
你是如此卑鄙像亨特的妻子一样
You're being so mean. Like Hunter's wife.
驼鹿！
Moose!
她不是我的最好的朋友她不是
She is not my BBF. She is not.
驼鹿！哦 来吧......
Moose! Oh, come on...
嘿 嘿我的男人！我们今晚的演出还是什么？
Hey, hey. My man! We on for tonight's show or what?
唐纳德特朗普 我们将会做得更多
We are gonna be making mucho Donald Trump.
托德 让我一个人呆着 - 你不会写纸
- Leave me alone, Todd. - You're not gonna make paper
在那个废话的警察警察装备 好吗？
in that bullshit bobby cop outfit, alright?
如果你真的需要钱 我可以赚钱 好吧？
If you really need money, I can make you money, alright?
轻松满足您的需求我继续说道好吗？
Give you what you need, easy. I go on in 15. Alright?
我可以教你如何喧嚣
I can teach you how to hustle.
我真的......我需要现金 穆斯 以一种糟糕的方式
And I really... I need the cash, Moose, in a bad way.
是的 买药？买药？买药？
Yeah, to buy drugs? To buy drugs? To buy drugs?
- 对你来说有什么关系？ - 我不是这样做的 托德！
- What does it matter to you? - I'm not doing it, Todd!
别管我别管我
Just leave me alone. Just leave me alone.
他妈的猫！
Fucking pussy!
你没有得到你想要的球
You don't have the balls to get what you want.
好的？我在这里得到了一个惊人的商机
Alright? I got an amazing business opportunity here
你知道吗？你正好盯着你看？
staring you right in the face, you know that?
我做得很好好的？
I'm done playing nice. Alright?
你会帮我做一些他妈的现金 婊子
You're gonna help me make some fucking cash, bitch.
我希望弗雷迪·克鲁格会来砍你的头
I wish Freddy Krueger would come and chop off your head.
它会在街上滚动 一辆卡车会挤压它
And it would roll in the street and a truck would squish it
血液会到处乱溅
and the blood would splatter everywhere.
每个人都会看到它！
And everyone would watch it!
无论如何你不值得
You're not worth it anyway.
驼鹿！
Moose!
我会遇到麻烦吗？我有麻烦吗？
Will I get in trouble? Am I in trouble?
你在跟我开玩笑吗？我以你为荣
Are you kidding me? I'm proud of you.
- 你为我感到骄傲？ - 是的
- You're proud of me? - Yes.
- 你为我感到骄傲？ - 你做的很好
- You're proud of me? - You did good.
人们不得不停止称我为缠扰者
People have to just stop calling me a stalker.
潜行者？
Stalker?
他们不得不停止称我为失败者
They have to stop calling me a loser.
因为我...
Because I...
甚至我的朋友都在呼唤我
Even my friends are calling me that.
新闻简报 驼鹿：托德不是你的朋友 男人
NEWSFLASH, MOOSE: Todd is not your friend, man.
我知道 但人们不得不停止挑剔我
I know, but people have to stop picking on me.
我要让他们停下来
I'm gonna make them stop.
邓巴先生
Mr. Dunbar.
我需要和你谈谈一些事情
I need to talk to you about something.
今天下午 你出去的时候
This afternoon, while you were out,
一些疯子走进了你的后院
some crazy man ran into your backyard.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我不得不吓跑他
I had to scare him away.
是的 好吧......
Yeah, well...
你确定这个疯子不是园丁吗？
you sure this crazy man wasn't the gardener?
不 这是不同的
No, this was something different.
好吧 无论你做了什么 它都有效
Well, whatever you did, it worked.
嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿 嘿过来
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Come here.
- 你还好吗？ - 我很害怕
- You alright? - I was so scared.
耶稣 你在颤抖
Jesus, you're shaking.
你还好吗？
You OK?
是啊
Yeah.
对不起我不应该
I'm sorry. I shouldn't.
对不起 那是......那是我的错
I'm sorry, that was... That's my fault.
- 我道歉 - 没关系
- I apologize. - It's OK.
它只是......我认为我们不能再这样做了
It's just... I don't think we can do that anymore.
好好
OK. OK.
多拉？
Dora?
是吗？
Yeah?
你 呃 你真的在​​这里做得很好
You, uh, you're really doing a great job around here.
感觉像家一样谢谢
Feels like a home again. Thank you.
嗯
Mm-hmm.
拉屎！
Shit!
- 嘿嘿嘿 - 啊
- Hey, hey, hey. - Ah.
我跟你说话的时候你得听我的
You got to listen to me when I talk to you.
对不起 海或我只是在听我的音乐
Sorry, señor. I was just listening to my music.
多拉说她今天看到有人潜入院子里
Dora said she saw somebody sneak into the yard today.
她很担心 你知道这让我很担心
She's concerned, which, you know, makes me very concerned.
你今天在院子里看到有人有异常吗？
Did you see someone strange in the yard today?
不 不 是或我只关注工作 就是全部
No, no, señor. I just focus on work, is all.
- 好的 - 干得好 是吗？
- Alright. - Just work, eh?
好看 帮我一个忙
OK. Look, do me a favor.
你在院子里看到有人怪我告诉我 好吗？
You see somebody strange in the yard you let me know, OK?
- 沙 沙 沙 沙 - 好的？
- Sí, sí, sí, sí. - Alright?
啥？或亨特 正在下雨 我无法完成
Señor Hunter, it's raining out, I cannot finish.
呃 也许我回家了？
Uh, maybe I go home?
- 是的是的 回家吧 - 格拉西亚斯
- Yeah. Yeah, go home. - Gracias.
好的来吧 我们迟到了
Alright. Come on, we're late.
你今天会给我一些目标 或者什么？
You gonna score me some goals today, or what?
- 是的- 好的进去进入......
- Yeah. - Alright. Get in. Get in...
不 不读它！
No, don't read it!
别读了！别读了！别读了！
Don't read it! Don't read it! Don't read it!
噢！
Ow!
救命！救命！救命！
Help! Help! Help!
我只是一个粉丝我只是...
I'm just a fan. I'm just...
-  阿宇达 阿宇达！ - 停止打我！
- Ayuda, ayuda! - Just stop hitting me!
-  阿宇达！ - 安静！
- Ayuda! - Be quiet!
天啊天啊
Oh, my gosh. Oh, my gosh.
你还好吗？
Are you OK?
对不起我很抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
这是一个流鼻血的人
That's a nosebleed.
那......那太糟糕了那很糟
That... That's bad. That's bad.
我流鼻血了这不好玩
I had a nosebleed. It wasn't fun.
但是你......你解决了
But you... you fix it.
你拿纸巾 你把它放在鼻子上......
You take paper towels and you put it up your nose...
没有激光
No laser.
没有警报
No alarm.
我......在......猎人......邓巴的......房子！
I'm... in... Hunter... Dunbar's... house!
“最好的怪物化妆品”
"Best Monster Makeup."
"Best Stunt."
“最好的特技”
穆斯在家里
Moose is in the house.
小心小心！
Watch out. Watch out!
这是......穆西
Here's... Moosey.
可怜的丹尼
Poor Danny.
所有的钱 没有冰淇淋
All that money, no ice cream.
这不是一个好脚本
This is not a good script.
他不应该这样做
He should not do it.
“两个睡觉”
"Two for sleep."
“一个用于失眠”
"One for insomnia."
可怜的邓巴
Poor Dunbar.
他不应该吸毒
He shouldn't be taking drugs.
“请出来
'Please come out.
- “妈妈累了” - 曲棍球运动员
- 'Mommy's tired.' - 'Hockey player.'
妈妈累了 胖
'Mommy's tired and fat.
“我们要生一个小宝宝
'We're gonna have a little baby.
“你看到了吗？不好笑
'Did you look at that? Not funny.
- “我很热” - 你很热吗？
- 'I'm hot.' - 'You're hot?'
- 是的 - 不......
- 'Yes.' - 'No...'
- “不要这样做” - “我也饿了”
- 'Don't do it.' - 'I'm hungry, too.'
我饿了我饿了 我很热
'I am hungry. I'm hungry and I'm hot.'
- 宝贝 你很热 - 它很美 但是......
- 'Babe, you are hot.' - 'It's beautiful, but...'
- 你太热了！ - 我不是
- 'You're hot!' - 'I am not.'
- “你在笑” - “你真是个傻瓜”
“你很热 宝贝
'You're hot, baby.
- 'You're smiling.' - 'You're such a jackass.'
“当你微笑时我爱”
'I love when you smile.'
- 好吧 没有更多相机 - 好吧 没有更多的相机
- 'OK, no more camera.' - 'Alright, no more camera.
“没有更多相机”
'No more camera.'
你在哪里 你的小狗屎？
Where are you, you little shit?
西装外套
Blazer.
要穿上西装外套
Gonna put on a blazer.
嘿
Hey.
不 我要过去了
No, I'm gonna pass.
因为看 看这就是事情
Because look, look. Here's the thing.
If I'm gonna be away on location away from Danny that long,
If I'm gonna be away on
location away from Danny that long,
如果我要远离丹尼那么久
If I'm gonna be away on location away from Danny that long,
他们让我值得拥有他们必须上来
they got to make it worth my while. They got to come up.
就是这样
That's just it.
无论如何 本周我想念你的妈妈
Anyways, I missed your mom this week.
是的 布伦达在另一个眼泪中
Yeah, Brenda's on another one of her tears.
不 我明白了我知道了我知道了我知道了
No, I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
嘿!你应该知道我 呃......
Hey! You should know I, uh...
再次吻了女仆
kissed the maid again.
我是个白痴
Cos I'm an idiot.
我不知道 伙计
I don't know, man.
有些怪人偷偷溜进屋子里
Some weirdo's been sneaking around the house.
是的 我稍后会和你谈谈 好吗？
Yeah, I'll talk to you later, OK?
好的 打电话给我
Alright, call me.
那么这是什么一回事？妈妈不会让你在家刷牙吗？
So, what's up? Mom doesn't make you brush your teeth at home?
- 不是很多 - 你是什么意思 “不是很多”？
- Not a lot. - What do you mean, "not a lot"?
没有你那么多
Not as much as you do.
我想昨晚我把牙刷放在地上了
I think I dropped your toothbrush on the ground last night.
不 我只是在开玩笑
Nah, I'm just kidding.
看 听我说
Look, listen to me.
仅仅因为妈妈没有执行规则
Just because Mom doesn't enforce a rule
并不意味着你不能做某事好的？
doesn't mean you can't not do something. Alright?
你必须在早上和晚上刷牙
You got to brush your teeth in the morning and at night,
因为这就是大男孩的所作所为大男孩们刷牙
because that's what big boys do. Big boys brush their teeth.
你现在变成了一个大男孩 所以你必须这样做
And you're becoming a big boy now, so you got to do it.
吐
Spit.
我不知道你为什么不跑水槽
I don't know why you don't run the sink.
- 妈妈怎么样？ - 很好
- How's Mom? - Good.
是吗？她让你上学好吗？
Yeah? She getting you to school OK?
- 是的- 诺言？
- Yeah. - Promise?
- 是的- 好
- Yeah. - OK.
你知道 如果你有任何需要或想要的东西
You know, if there's anything you ever need or want,
- 你可以打电话给我 对吗？ - 是的
- you can call me, right? - Yeah.
如果你有任何问题 或者其他什么
If you ever got any problems, or whatever.
是啊
Yeah.
好的亲爱的 我爱你
Alright. I love you, buddy.
睡得好 好吗？
Sleep well, alright?
“我想知道我们买了多少次同样的作品？
'I wonder how many times we bought the same work?
“嘿 我的意思是 为教会祈祷 对吧？来吧
'Hey, I mean, praying's for church, huh? Come on.'
“我最近没在教堂见过你”
'I haven't seen you in church lately.'
“好吧 我去教堂的意义不大
'Well, not much sense in my going to church.
“你还记得我们小时候的一次 我们在外面吗？
'Do you remember one time when we were small, we were out here?
“那是在那边
'It was from right over there.
“我从树后面跳了出来
'I jumped out at you from behind the tree
和爷爷兴奋得振作起来 他向我握拳
'and grandpa got all excited and he shook his fist at me.
“他说 ”男孩 你会被该死的“
'And he said, "Boy, you'll be damned to hell."
- 还记得吗？ - 进来
- 'Remember that?' - Come on in.
“你以前真的很害怕”
'You used to really be scared.'
- 约翰尼 - “你还是害怕”
- 'Johnny.' - 'You're still afraid.'
“现在停下来 我的意思是”
'Stop it now, I mean it.'
哦......别介意我的小穆西
Oh... Don't mind my little Moosey.
“芭芭拉 他们会来接你的”
'They're coming to get you, Barbara.'
停下来你是无知的
'Stop it. You're ignorant.'
“芭芭拉 他们会为你而来”
'They're coming for you, Barbara.'
停下来你的表现就像一个孩子
'Stop it. You're acting like a child.'
“他们会为你而来
'They're coming for you.
“看 现在有一个”
'Look, there comes one of them now.'
- “他会听到你的” - 他现在来了
- 'He'll hear you.' - 'Here he comes now.
- 我出去了 - 约翰尼！
- 'I'm getting out.' - 'Johnny!'
你可以用一些音乐吗？
You OK with some music?
- 你喜欢一个小软饼干乐队？ - 当然
- You like a little Limp Bizkit? - Sure.
- 你喜欢一个小软饼干乐队？ - 是的
- You like a little Bizkit? - Yeah.
我以前常常听这个
I used to listen to this back in the day.
哦 天哪 这很好那很好
Oh, my God, that is nice. That is nice.
啊 我们走了 宝贝
Ah, here we go, baby.
留在这儿
Stay here.
你到底在这做什么？
What the hell are you doing back here?
- 我只是......我只是......我...我...  - “我......只是......”
- I just... I just... I... I... - "I... just..."
也许我第一次没弄清楚
Maybe I didn't make myself clear the first time,
你口吃他妈的
you stuttering fuck.
你想活着看明天吗？
You wanna live to see tomorrow?
- 是的先生 - 然后你远离我
- Yes, sir. - Then you stay away from me,
而你远离我的儿子
and you stay away from my son.
再也不会涉足这个社区
And never set foot in this neighborhood again.
- 你明白吗？咦？ - 是的先生是的先生
- Do you understand? Huh? - Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
现在 我再次在这附近找到你
Now, I catch you in this neighborhood again,
到目前为止 我会把我的雷明顿霰弹枪推到你的屁股上
I will shove my Remington shotgun so far up your ass
在你的余生中 你将会击中子弹和血液
you'll be shitting bullets and blood for the rest of your life.
你明白？我想让你说出来
You understand? I want you to say it.
- 我想听你说 - “我会把子弹击中......”
- I want to hear you say it. - "I'll be shitting bullets..."
不 你这个白痴！说你再也不会来这个街区了
No, you idiot! Say you'll never come in this neighborhood again.
说吧说吧！
Say it. Say it!
我永远不会回到这里
I'll never come back here.
- 该死的！ - 永远不会
- Goddamn right! - Never.
回到你来自哪里 你跟踪者！
Go back where you came from, you stalker!
我不是跟踪者！
I am not a stalker!
噢！
Ow!
我还好吗？
Am I alright?
哦 他是一切 我什么都不是
Oh, he's everything, I'm nothing.
好吧 让我告诉你一件事 邓巴先生 邓巴先生！
Well, let me tell you something, Mr. Dunbar, Mr. Dummybar!
你还没有...
You have not...
我再说一遍 你没有做出最好的选择
I repeat, you have not made the best choices.
I repeat, you have
not made the best choices.
“鬼火车”真是太愚蠢了
I repeat, you have not made the best choices.
"Ghost Train" was so stupid.
真是太愚蠢了
It was so stupid.
谁一直坚持你？
And who stuck by you all the time?
我！我做到了！
Me! I did!
这是一场噩梦！这是一个疯狂的噩梦！
This is a nightmare! This is a freakin' nightmare!
没有！不行！
No! It is not OK!
不行！
It is not OK!
你不好
You're not nice.
你是一个很大的假货！
You're a big fake!
“你不是害怕他们寻求报复吗？”
'Aren't you afraid of them seeking revenge?'
“复仇是我的中间名”
'Revenge is my middle name.'
你只是整天假装 这就是你所做的一切
You just pretend all day, that's all you do.
任何人都可以做到这一点
Anybody can do that.
任何人都可以做到！
Anybody can do that!
“吻我 维哥”
'Kiss me, Vigo.'
驼鹿！
Moose!
驼鹿 开放！我知道你在那里
Moose, open up! I know you're in there.
你看起来很糟糕
You look like shit.
它闻起来像汽油
It smells like gasoline.
所以...
So...
一直在使用你的星辰地图应用访问一些朋友？
been using your, uh, Star Map app to visit some friends?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
您一直在使用社交媒体
You've been using your social media
播放犯罪活动
to broadcast criminal activities.
在他睡觉的时候亲吻亨特·邓巴？
Kissing Hunter Dunbar while he's sleeping?
你是正式的想法
You're officially out of your mind.
我可以把这些照片展示给警察
I could show these photos to the police
你会遇到麻烦
and you'd be in trouble.
不要那样做不要那样做
Don't do that. Don't do that.
好吧 你什么都不听
Well, you don't listen to anything.
你不听我的话 而且......你不遵守规则
You don't listen to me, and... you don't follow rules.
- 给我你的手机 - 没有
- Give me your phone. - No.
给我你的手机！给我你的手机或者就是这样好？
Give me your phone! Give me your phone or this is it. OK?
没有借钱了没有更多建议没有更多
No more borrowing money. No more advice. No more anything.
那是你要的吗？失去你的最好的朋友？
Is that what you want? To lose your BBF?
失去你在全世界唯一的朋友？
To lose your only friend in the entire world?
你的意思是！
You're mean!
好吧 就是这样 莉娅看这个你被封锁了
OK, that's it, Leah. Look at this. You're blocked.
你被我的社交媒体封锁了你走！
You're blocked from my social media. You go!
你走！你离开这里！
You go! You get out of here!
我想保护你
I'm trying to protect you.
什么他妈的？什么他妈的？
What the fuck? What the fuck?
什么他妈的？
What the fuck?
嘿!
Hey!
救命！
Help!
Oh, you fucking idiot.
哦 你他妈的白痴
你他妈的白痴
You fucking idiot.
你是愚蠢的心理跟踪者
You stupid psycho stalker.
你他妈的......救命！
You fucking... Help!
你一直在拼图
You've been Jigsawed.
游戏结束
Game over.
救命！
Help!
妈的妈的
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
等等 等等 等等嘿 听我说听我说
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Hey, listen to me. Listen to me.
等等等待！等待！等待！
Wait, wait. Wait! Wait! Wait!
我骗了亨特邓巴
I fooled Hunter Dunbar.
我骗了亨特邓巴！我是个好演员
I fooled Hunter Dunbar! I'm such a good actor.
I fooled Hunter Dunbar!
I'm such a good actor.
- 你出局了吗？ - 不过你也很好
I fooled Hunter Dunbar! I'm such a good actor.
- You outta your mind? - You were good, too, though.
你真的很好你很好
You were really good. You were good.
你比杰米·李·柯蒂斯好
You were better than Jamie Lee Curtis.
好
OK.
我砍你了吗？
Did I cut you?
哇靠
Holy crap.
哦 这不好
Oh, this isn't good.
Oh, this is not good.
你不合适让我走
You're out of line. Let me go.
你想要什么？
What do you want?
你为什么一直这么生气？
Why are you so angry all the time?
我应该是那个对你生气的人
I should be the one angry at you.
你为什么这么关心我？
Why do you care so much about me?
因为我爱你我爱你我爱你
Because I love you. And I love you. And I love you.
我......我看过你所有的电影
And I... and I've seen all your movies.
而且我喜欢你的电影我......认为你是最好的
And I love your movies. And I... think you're the best.
解开这些绳索 你是一个婊子的儿子解开他们！
Untie these ropes, you son of a bitch. Untie them!
不要对我如此吝啬！停下来！
Stop being so mean to me! Stop it!
什么？你在寻找15分钟的名气？咦？
What? You looking for your 15 minutes of fame? Huh?
你想结束每晚的新闻吗？
You wanna end up on the nightly news?
他们会称你为怪物
They're gonna call you a monster.
包里面有什么？
What's in the bag?
猎人 请耐心等待这是个惊喜
Hunter, be patient, please. It's a surprise.
准备好了？
OK, ready?
金发先生
Mr. Blonde.
- 神圣的狗屎！不 - 金发先生
- Holy shit! No. - Mr. Blonde.
不不不等待等待等待等待啊！
No, no, no. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Ahh!
别烧我！停止！停止！停止！嘿!
Don't burn me! Stop! Stop! Stop! Hey!
这里没有煤气 只是水
There's no gas in here, it's just water.
我不会烧毁你的房子或什么都没有
I'm not gonna burn your house down or nothing.
来吧
Come on.
对不起 我对你很吝啬
I'm sorry I was mean to you.
你是我生命中最卑微的人
You're the meanest person I've ever known in my life.
让我补偿你
Let me make it up to you.
我会签署你想要的任何东西
I'll sign whatever you want.
我甚至还有“饥饿的人”中的仪式匕首
I even have the ceremonial dagger from "The Hungry Ones".
我能搞定我现在可以签名
I could get it. I can sign it right now.
你觉得我是个什么样的白痴？
What kind of moron do you think I am?
我认为没有人是白痴
I don't think anybody's a moron.
- 是的你是 - 不 我没有
- Yes, you do. - No, I don't.
- Yes, you do.
- No, I don't.
我知道你对我的看法你以为我是一个跟踪者！
- Yes, you do. - No, I don't.
And I know what you think of me. You think I'm a stalker!
- 不 - 是的 你做到了
- No. - Yes, you do.
但我会去你的每一部电影
But I go to every one of your movies.
即使是蹩脚的
Even the crappy ones.
你必须明白一些事情
You've got to understand something.
你掌握着这种关系的力量
You hold the power in this relationship.
你是粉丝 没有你 我什么都不是
You're a fan, and I'm nothing without you.
再说一次
Say that again.
- 什么？ - 说了什么 说出来
- What? - What you said, say it.
你是粉丝
You are a fan.
没有你...
Without you...
我什么也不是
I'm nothing.
你饿了吗？
Are you hungry?
我饿了
I'm hungry.
你呆在那里你不动
You stay there. Don't you move.
你不动
Don't you move.
Holy fuck.
圣洁他妈的
圣洁他妈的圣洁他妈的
Holy fuck. Holy fuck.
圣洁他妈的！圣洁他妈的！
Holy fuck! Holy fuck!
穆斯不只是越过界限
'Moose didn't just cross the line,
“他妈的他妈的
'he fucking nuked it.
“老实说 我也会害怕
'Honestly, I'd be scared, too.
“可怜的穆西”
'Poor Moosey.'
嘿
Hey.
过来
Come here.
让我为你签一个
Let me sign one for you.
驼鹿？是吗？
Moose? Is that it?
“要......穆斯”
"To... Moose."
“带着爱 ”
"With love,."
“亨特邓巴”
"Hunter Dunbar."
芭芭拉
Barbara.
哦 芭芭拉
Oh, Barbara.
芭芭拉 他们来找你
They're coming to get you, Barbara.
芭芭拉
Barbara.
芭芭拉 他们来找你
They're coming to get you, Barbara.
“活死人之夜”
"Night of the Living Dead".
你为什么不知道？
Why don't you know that?
我开始思考了
I'm starting to think
你对恐怖图片一无所知
you don't know anything about horror pictures.
抱歉让人失望
Sorry to disappoint.
这个...
This...
它不是......它还不错这不是一种享受
It's not... It's not bad. It just isn't a treat.
我想丹尼会长大后恨你
I think Danny's gonna grow up hating you.
不要谈论我的儿子
Don't talk about my son.
冰箱里根本没有冰淇淋
You have no ice cream in the fridge at all.
然后我会继续努力
Then I'll work on it.
看......在这里 看尝尝它尝尝它
Look... Here, look. Taste it. Taste it.
前进
Go ahead.
看到？看到？
See? See?
这不甜这不是一种享受
It's not sweet. It's not a treat.
这不是一种享受
It's not a treat.
但他们需要品尝美味的食物
But they need good tasting treats.
然后恐怖图片
And then horror pictures.
- 他会记住这个 - 我会买冰淇淋 好吗？
- He's gonna remember this. - I'll get ice cream, OK?
我会得到它的
I'll get it.
如果你解开这些绳索 我现在会给他一些东西
I'll get him some right now if you untie these ropes.
我做不到
I can't do that.
当然可以
Of course you can.
你会让我陷入困境
You're gonna get me in trouble.
没有
No.
- 你会伤到我吗？ - 不 我不会这样做
- Are you gonna hurt me? - No. I won't do that.
我知道你是个好人
I know you're a good person.
我似乎很卑鄙......生气......
I seem mean and... angry...
但我只是害怕 伙计我只是...
but I'm just scared, man. I'm just...
我真的很害怕
I'm just really scared.
我也知道你也是
And I know you are, too.
你害怕吗？
You scared?
你只想离开 对吧？
You just wanna leave, right?
那没关系 伙计没关系
That's alright, man. That's OK.
我不会报警
这是你和我之间的承诺
That's alright, man. That's OK.
- 没有警察？ - 没有警察
- 没有警察 - 在那之后...
That's alright, man. That's OK.
这感觉不太好
This doesn't feel good.
听我说 好吗？
Hear me out, OK?
如果你让我走 我保证......
If you let me go, I pledge...
我...我向上帝发誓...我向上帝发誓
I... I swear to God... I swear to God,
I will not call the police.
我...我向上帝发誓...我向上帝发誓
That's a promise between you and me.
- No police? - No police.
我...我向上帝发誓...我向上帝发誓
- No police. - And after that...
我会签署你想要的任何东西
I will sign whatever you want,
无论何时何地 在您的余生中
whenever you want, for the rest of your life.
这是另一个承诺
That's another promise.
这是一生的承诺
That is a lifetime commitment.
- 你签了我？ - 真正的粉丝
- You'd sign for me? - For a real fan.
你会签我吗？
You'll sign for me?
你会亲自给我签名吗？
You'll sign for me personally?
因为易趣上的所有内容都是谎言 所以这是假的
Because everything on eBay is a lie, it's a fake.
见鬼 是的
Hell, yeah.
- 是吗？ - 见鬼 是的！
- Yeah? - Hell, yeah!
你真聪明你很聪明
You're smart. You're real smart.
我会亲自给你签名
I will sign everything personally to you.
- 你叫什么名字？ - 驼鹿
- What's your name? - Moose.
- 你说过驼鹿吗？ - 驼鹿
- Did you say Moose? - Moose.
好好的 穆斯
OK. OK, Moose.
所有签名都将亲自签名
All the autographs will be personally autographed
对你 穆斯
to you, Moose.
是吗？
Is that it?
只是不要伤害我的孩子
Just don't hurt my kid.
伤害你的孩子？瓦...
Hurt your kid? Wh...
我永远不会伤害你的儿子！
I would never ever, ever, ever hurt your son!
永远！
Ever!
你为什么这么说呢？
Why would you even say that?
让我走吧 伙计
Just let me go, man.
我是演员 好吗？
I'm an actor, alright?
好吧 演员他们尝试这种技术
Well, actors they try this technique
称为可视化
called visualization.
那是什么？那是什么？
What is that? What is that?
这意味着想象
It means to imagine.
你想和我一起尝试这种技巧吗？
You wanna try this technique with me?
好的 在这里过来
Alright, here. Come here.
跪下来 舒服一点
Kneel down, get comfortable.
放下你的肩膀放松
Drop your shoulders. Relax.
来吧 放弃他们感觉很舒服放轻松
Go ahead, drop 'em. Just feel comfortable. Just relax.
我需要你深吸一口气
I need you to take a deep breath in.
是啊
Yeah.
现在我想让你想象你和我
Now I want you to imagine you and me.
- 你和我？ - 是的你看到了我们？
- You and me? - Yeah. You see us?
- 我做 - 好的
- I do. - Alright.
我们要做的第一件事就是
First thing we're gonna do, is
我们要改变这些脏衣服
we're gonna change these dirty clothes.
我们要脱掉汗水 这种血液和这种汽油
We're gonna take off this sweat, this blood and this gasoline,
我们要穿上一些新鲜的哑弹
and we're gonna put on some fresh new duds.
穆斯 我们看起来很漂亮我们会好看的
We're gonna look spiffy, Moose. We're gonna look good.
然后我们要去镇上
And then we're gonna go out on the town.
我们要去那些好莱坞花哨的关节之一
We're gonna go to one of those Hollywood fancy joints.
穆索与弗兰克？我们要去穆索与弗兰克？
Musso & Frank's? We're going to Musso & Frank's?
无论你想要什么 伙计
Wherever you want, man.
我们会去任何你想去的地方我会打电话给我的经理
We'll go wherever you want. I'll call my manager,
无论你想去哪里 他都会给我们一张桌子
he'll get us a table wherever you wanna go.
当它完成后
And when it's all done,
我们会买一大碗巧克力冰淇淋
we'll get a big bowl of chocolate ice cream.
草莓草莓冰淇淋
Strawberry. Strawberry ice cream.
是啊！是啊耶耶耶
Yeah! Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
草莓冰淇淋 麋 当然当然
Strawberry ice cream, Moose, of course. Of course.
然后......然后我们会回到我的位置
And then... and then we'll go back to my place
并投了几部我的动作片
and throw on a couple of my action films,
并在高清电视上观看它们
and watch them on the HD TV.
这听起来不错 伙计？
Does that sound good, man?
- 我爱你我爱你 - 啊 你 我
- I love you. I love you. - Ah, you, me,
几个动作片
couple of action flicks,
和一些草莓冰淇淋吧？
and some strawberry ice cream, right?
- 只是......只有你和我 伙计 - 就咱俩
- Just... just you and I, man. - Just you and me.
等等 我们只是先取下这些绳索 你知道吗？
Wait, we just got to take these ropes off first, you know?
- 好好 - 是吗？好的
- OK. OK. - Yeah? Alright.
好
OK.
伙计 等到你看到这个系列
Man, wait till you see this collection.
- 是吗？ - 是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
这些是一些严重的结你在哪里学到这些？
These are some serious knots. Where'd you learn these?
-  油管 -  油管？
- YouTube. - YouTube?
油管上教你一切
YouTube. Teaches you everything.
教你各种各样的结 C结 桶结
Teaches you all kind of knots. C knots, barrel knots.
把它放在这里 伙计
Put it here, pal.
你不能离开 穆斯
You can't leave, Moose.
没了你我什么都不是
I'm nothing without you.
我喜欢你的电影
I just like your movies.
天啊！
Oh, man!
天哪！
Holy shit!
哦 我的上帝！
Oh, my God!
发生了什么？
What happened?
好的 你知道吗？没关系 我们......
OK, you know what? It's OK, we're...
我会帮你的我就在这里 伙计 好吗？
I'm gonna get you some help. I'm right here, buddy, OK?
和亨特？他是演员
'And Hunter? He's an actor.'
哦 上帝 拜托 上帝
Oh, God, please, God.
“而且他是幸存者
'And he's a survivor.
“我担心这是多拉”
'It's Dora that I'm worried about.'
我的头！
My head!
我知道我知道
'I know, I know,
穆斯失去了他的手和他的眼睛
'Moose lost his hand and his eye.
“但最终 他看起来就像是荣誉徽章”
'But eventually, he looked at it like a badge of honor.'
没戴眼镜我看不见它说什么？
I can't see without my glasses. What does it say?
它说 “露易丝......露易丝弗莱彻”
It says, "Louise... Louise Fletcher."
路易丝弗莱彻 她不是一个好护士
Louise Fletcher, she's not a good nurse.
- 不 她不是
- No. - She's not.
不 她不是
No, she's not.
我不是跟踪者！
I am not a stalker!
翻译：抢鲜字幕组（人工智能翻译版）
Fresh Chinese Subtitles